[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 5, "question": "What are you two talking about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "two", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "They do say the --", "answer_tokens": ["They", "do", "say", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What's happening?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "The countdown really is beginning now.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "countdown", "really", "is", "beginning", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "The bride is on the move to the palace?", "question_tokens": ["The", "bride", "is", "on", "the", "move", "to", "the", "palace", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I suspect that was quite an emotional journey.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "suspect", "that", "was", "quite", "an", "emotional", "journey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "What she's doing with disco balls?", "question_tokens": ["What", "she", "'s", "doing", "with", "disco", "balls", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "You know, this is expected earlier in the week, that three of the rooms in the palace are going to be transformed into a nightclub.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "this", "is", "expected", "earlier", "in", "the", "week", ",", "that", "three", "of", "the", "rooms", "in", "the", "palace", "are", "going", "to", "be", "transformed", "into", "a", "nightclub", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "And if Prince Harry's in charge of the party, it's going to be a big party, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "Prince", "Harry", "'s", "in", "charge", "of", "the", "party", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "big", "party", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "It's going to be a big party.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "big", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Henry VIII"]}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "How important is it, do you think, constitutionally that William and Kate stay together?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "constitutionally", "that", "William", "and", "Kate", "stay", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, as it turns out, you can divorce anybody in the royal family and it will be OK, which we've kind of established ever since Henry VIII up through the present day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "it", "turns", "out", ",", "you", "can", "divorce", "anybody", "in", "the", "royal", "family", "and", "it", "will", "be", "OK", ",", "which", "we", "'ve", "kind", "of", "established", "ever", "since", "Henry", "VIII", "up", "through", "the", "present", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William", "Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "It's not as sexy, is it, as a monarch monarchy, where no one can get rid of them?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "as", "sexy", ",", "is", "it", ",", "as", "a", "monarch", "monarchy", ",", "where", "no", "one", "can", "get", "rid", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "It's because you're in the star system and you're in the star system.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "because", "you", "'re", "in", "the", "star", "system", "and", "you", "'re", "in", "the", "star", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "That it has to be the oldest boy, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "it", "has", "to", "be", "the", "oldest", "boy", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "It's absurd.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "absurd", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "I think it's too early to say is the first point I'd make.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "too", "early", "to", "say", "is", "the", "first", "point", "I", "'d", "make", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What do you feel about the security?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "security", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, I think it's inevitable with any world event -- and this is a world event now -- security has to be paramount.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "inevitable", "with", "any", "world", "event", "--", "and", "this", "is", "a", "world", "event", "now", "--", "security", "has", "to", "be", "paramount", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What do you think she'll be hoping from this wedding?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "she", "'ll", "be", "hoping", "from", "this", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I think she'll be hoping that they're happy fundamentally.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'ll", "be", "hoping", "that", "they", "'re", "happy", "fundamentally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What do you think she would have made of all this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "she", "would", "have", "made", "of", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "I think she'd have been tremendously proud.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'d", "have", "been", "tremendously", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "How would she have coped psychologically do you think with William finding a rival love in many ways?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "she", "have", "coped", "psychologically", "do", "you", "think", "with", "William", "finding", "a", "rival", "love", "in", "many", "ways", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I think it would have been really tough for her, this year in particular.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "would", "have", "been", "really", "tough", "for", "her", ",", "this", "year", "in", "particular", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "What was she really like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "she", "really", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "She was amusing.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "amusing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Did you worry about Kate Middleton?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "worry", "about", "Kate", "Middleton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "I worry a little but I think Kate has sorted it out.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "worry", "a", "little", "but", "I", "think", "Kate", "has", "sorted", "it", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "It's hard to harangue a man who was forced through duty to marry the woman who wasn't really the love of his life, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "harangue", "a", "man", "who", "was", "forced", "through", "duty", "to", "marry", "the", "woman", "who", "was", "n't", "really", "the", "love", "of", "his", "life", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, yes, it tells you a lot about his weakness.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "it", "tells", "you", "a", "lot", "about", "his", "weakness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1981"]}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "ORGAN: As we prepare for the big day, how does it feel for you compared to 1981?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "As", "we", "prepare", "for", "the", "big", "day", ",", "how", "does", "it", "feel", "for", "you", "compared", "to", "1981", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I don't find it as exciting as 1981.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "find", "it", "as", "exciting", "as", "1981", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1981"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Do you still have any contact with William?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "have", "any", "contact", "with", "William", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "I didn't have contact with William, unlike you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "have", "contact", "with", "William", ",", "unlike", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Oh, is that all?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "is", "that", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "That's all it is, 300.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "all", "it", "is", ",", "300", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "For the dinner?", "question_tokens": ["For", "the", "dinner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "For the dinner, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "the", "dinner", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "What will the pressure be like on the chefs for this one?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "the", "pressure", "be", "like", "on", "the", "chefs", "for", "this", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Well, it will be enormous.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "will", "be", "enormous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What would you -- what would you come up with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "--", "what", "would", "you", "come", "up", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Well, think you've got to keep your British.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "think", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "keep", "your", "British", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Gulls eggs?", "question_tokens": ["Gulls", "eggs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "HITE: Gulls eggs.", "answer_tokens": ["HITE", ":", "Gulls", "eggs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Are they very rich?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "very", "rich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Really rich.", "answer_tokens": ["Really", "rich", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "And a pudding?", "question_tokens": ["And", "a", "pudding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "You got to go for Eton Mess.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "got", "to", "go", "for", "Eton", "Mess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "What is an Eton Mess?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "an", "Eton", "Mess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "It's very simple.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What does it mean to you to be British?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "you", "to", "be", "British", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "It's -- well, one, I have an Italian mother.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "well", ",", "one", ",", "I", "have", "an", "Italian", "mother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "What are the values you think -- when we have a royal wedding, when the world looks at us, what are the values that still remain quintessentially British?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "values", "you", "think", "--", "when", "we", "have", "a", "royal", "wedding", ",", "when", "the", "world", "looks", "at", "us", ",", "what", "are", "the", "values", "that", "still", "remain", "quintessentially", "British", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I think it brings out the best in people and reminds them of the great country that they've been brought up in and all those values.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "brings", "out", "the", "best", "in", "people", "and", "reminds", "them", "of", "the", "great", "country", "that", "they", "'ve", "been", "brought", "up", "in", "and", "all", "those", "values", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "I think it's going to be a great day, Friday, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "great", "day", ",", "Friday", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Do you know what, not just a great day.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", ",", "not", "just", "a", "great", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sharon Osbourne"]}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "In your pub?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "pub", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Sitting next to Sharon Osbourne in the rival box.", "answer_tokens": ["Sitting", "next", "to", "Sharon", "Osbourne", "in", "the", "rival", "box", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Oh, you know that?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "I know some things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "some", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Are you a romantic man?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "romantic", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I think so, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "So when the big moment comes, when they come out on the balcony and they prepare for what we imagine will be the most viewed kiss in history, will you be feeling a little warm and cuddly inside?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "the", "big", "moment", "comes", ",", "when", "they", "come", "out", "on", "the", "balcony", "and", "they", "prepare", "for", "what", "we", "imagine", "will", "be", "the", "most", "viewed", "kiss", "in", "history", ",", "will", "you", "be", "feeling", "a", "little", "warm", "and", "cuddly", "inside", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I don't -- I guess if that's the definition of romantic, than maybe I'm not romantic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "guess", "if", "that", "'s", "the", "definition", "of", "romantic", ",", "than", "maybe", "I", "'m", "not", "romantic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "You're going to be watching?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "watching", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I'll be on stage that night.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "be", "on", "stage", "that", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What time are you on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "time", "are", "you", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Seven thirty.", "answer_tokens": ["Seven", "thirty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "How are you finding British beer, because we believe it's the best in the world?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "finding", "British", "beer", ",", "because", "we", "believe", "it", "'s", "the", "best", "in", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "It's very good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "You into real ale, into a hand pumped real foaming bitter?", "question_tokens": ["You", "into", "real", "ale", ",", "into", "a", "hand", "pumped", "real", "foaming", "bitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Have you spoken to her majesty, the queen, in the build up to the wedding?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "spoken", "to", "her", "majesty", ",", "the", "queen", ",", "in", "the", "build", "up", "to", "the", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Oh yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Can I use that word on this show?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "use", "that", "word", "on", "this", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "You just did.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "just", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Do the British royals curtsy to you when they see you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "the", "British", "royals", "curtsy", "to", "you", "when", "they", "see", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "No, they know I'm trustworthy.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "know", "I", "'m", "trustworthy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Are you as excited about the wedding, as everybody else seems to be?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "excited", "about", "the", "wedding", ",", "as", "everybody", "else", "seems", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "No, I'm not, really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Can I say this on CNN?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "say", "this", "on", "CNN", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I think you can.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "IN", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Well, it's been going on and on and on.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "going", "on", "and", "on", "and", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "What do you think of both William, our future king, and his choice of bride?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "both", "William", ",", "our", "future", "king", ",", "and", "his", "choice", "of", "bride", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "She is beautiful.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "is", "beautiful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I think she is .", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "When Charles married Diana, where were you then?", "question_tokens": ["When", "Charles", "married", "Diana", ",", "where", "were", "you", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "I was around.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"], "LOCATION": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Did you ever things could have panned out differently?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "things", "could", "have", "panned", "out", "differently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "He liked me.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "liked", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Have you spoken to her majesty, the queen, in the build- up to the weddings?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "spoken", "to", "her", "majesty", ",", "the", "queen", ",", "in", "the", "build-", "up", "to", "the", "weddings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Oh, yes, she calls me quite a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "she", "calls", "me", "quite", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Have you got a gift for the royal couple?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "a", "gift", "for", "the", "royal", "couple", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Yes, I bought them -- I thought of all the gifts that people from other nations will be giving them.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "bought", "them", "--", "I", "thought", "of", "all", "the", "gifts", "that", "people", "from", "other", "nations", "will", "be", "giving", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Grill?", "question_tokens": ["Grill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Grill.", "answer_tokens": ["Grill", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "One of those fat free grills?", "question_tokens": ["One", "of", "those", "fat", "free", "grills", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "A fat free grill.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "fat", "free", "grill", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Did you know that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "I didn't know that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "know", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Duchess of York", "Fergie"], "PERSON": ["Sarah"]}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Are there Scrabble players watching?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "Scrabble", "players", "watching", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "I heard speculation that you may have taken the seat that was originally reserved for Sarah, Duchess of York, for Fergie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "heard", "speculation", "that", "you", "may", "have", "taken", "the", "seat", "that", "was", "originally", "reserved", "for", "Sarah", ",", "Duchess", "of", "York", ",", "for", "Fergie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "Are you fans of theirs?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "fans", "of", "theirs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "Look, I am a royalist, viewers.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "am", "a", "royalist", ",", "viewers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "What advice do you give to the other royals about how to sustain the terrible media pressure you have had to withstand?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "do", "you", "give", "to", "the", "other", "royals", "about", "how", "to", "sustain", "the", "terrible", "media", "pressure", "you", "have", "had", "to", "withstand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "Look, they have withstood the media pressure.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "they", "have", "withstood", "the", "media", "pressure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "Larry King?", "question_tokens": ["Larry", "King", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "He's still alive?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "still", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "He said you could be wife number nine, if you play your cards right.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "said", "you", "could", "be", "wife", "number", "nine", ",", "if", "you", "play", "your", "cards", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "TO", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "How do you feel about our future king of England marrying a commoner?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "our", "future", "king", "of", "England", "marrying", "a", "commoner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "Well, the word commoner doesn't mean much to Australians, and certainly not to Americans.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "word", "commoner", "does", "n't", "mean", "much", "to", "Australians", ",", "and", "certainly", "not", "to", "Americans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "Would you allow the monarchs to behead people they didn't like, wives, husbands, that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "allow", "the", "monarchs", "to", "behead", "people", "they", "did", "n't", "like", ",", "wives", ",", "husbands", ",", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "There are some people you and I would be very, very heavy to behead.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "some", "people", "you", "and", "I", "would", "be", "very", ",", "very", "heavy", "to", "behead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]